Guide to the Margaret Marshall Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Family Papers, 1936-73; Series IV; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  - Fleck, Judith
    - Checkbook registers, 1970-71 (Box 16, Folder 394)
    - Correspondence, 1971-73 (Box 16, Folder 395-404)
    - Estate papers, 1971-72 (Box 16, Folder 405)
    - Income taxes, 1969-72 (Box 16, Folder 406)
    - Medical bills, 1969-71 (Box 16, Folder 407)
    - Obituary, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 408)
    - Passports, 1949, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 409)
    - Vital records, 1931-71 (Box 16, Folder 410)
  - Insurance policy, [1965?], 1969 (Box 16, Folder 411)
  - Jewelry designs, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 412-13)
  - Memorial service, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 414)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 415)
  - Passport, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 416)
  - Photographs
    - Fleck family, 1948, 1964, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 417)
    - Gaines family, 1868, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 418)
    - Marr, Sarah Gaines, 1965, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 419)
    - Marshall family, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 420)
    - Marshall, Margaret, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 421)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-72 (Box 17, Folder 422)
    - Roxabel, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 423)
    - Unidentified, 1955, 1964, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 424)
  - Printed works
    - American Men of Letters series, 1946-49 (Box 17, Folder 425)
    - Auden, W. H., 1970-73 (Box 17, Folder 426)
    - Book reviews, 1954-73, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 427-29)
    - Clark, Evans, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 430)
    - Clippings, miscellaneous, 1891-73 (Box 17, Folder 431-33)
    - Fleck family, 1949, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 434)
    - Krutch, Joseph Wood, 1967, 1900 (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - Miscellaneous printed material, 1956-71, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - The Nation, 1953-65 (Box 17, Folder 437-38)
    - The New Leader, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - The Paris Review, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Obituaries, miscellaneous, 1956-71, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Programs, 1948, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Publishing, 1964-70 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Schwartz, Delmore, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 444)
    - Soviet policy, 1952-73 (Box 17, Folder 445-46)
    - Vayo, Alvarez del, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 447)
- Oversize, 1886
  - Gaines, Robert H.: obituary, 1886 (Box 18, Folder 448)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.25; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 19: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folders 8-11, 13-14, 16, 18-21, 23, 26, 31, 36, 38 (Box 19, Folder 449-50)
  - Box 2, folders 41, 48-49, 54, 57, 59 64-65 (Box 19, Folder 451)
  - Box 3, folders 92, 99, 102, 106 Box 4, folder 139 Box 10, folder 254-55 Box 11, folder 276 (Box 19, Folder 452)
  - Box 13, folders 308-10, 312 Box 14, folders 336-37 (Box 19, Folder 453)
  - Box 14, folders 339, 343, 346, 353, 361 Box 18, folders 468, 488 (Box 19, Folder 454)